<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blook&#39;s bog</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content on blook&#39;s bog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 18:27:58 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Year in Books 2021</title>
      <link>/posts/2021-year-in-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 18:24:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2021-year-in-books/</guid>
      <description>2021 was another year for the books, both for myself and for the world. The world was ravaged with another year of the COVID-19 pandemic and the many variants of the virus, but we saw some hope with vaccines and booster shots. We collectively defined new ways of living, new comfort boundaries. It’s safe to say the world has changed forever. Personally, I had some pretty big life changes as well – I finished my first full year at my full-time job and I moved to a new city and made all of the lifestyle changes that come with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year in Books 2020</title>
      <link>/posts/2020-year-in-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2020 18:24:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2020-year-in-books/</guid>
      <description>We’re in our final week of 2020, and while just about everything around us has changed, my annual summary of the books I’ve read this year is still in order. Every year, when I write this post, I mention how the books I read are a reflection of my trains of thought during that year. This year, that couldn’t be more true, and as you’ll see from the 40+ books I’ll share with you today, 2020 had me asking questions, learning, riding emotional rollercoasters, getting lost in stories, and trying to find my way in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 19 Books of 2019</title>
      <link>/posts/2019-year-in-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2019 18:24:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2019-year-in-books/</guid>
      <description>2019 was filled with things that changed the way I think about the world. Some of those things were caused through experiences, but a lot of them were ideas I found in books. My goal was to read 23 books in 2019, and as of Christmas, I have read 32 books (28 cover-to-cover and 4 that I read bits and pieces of, or abandoned somewhere in the middle).
In this article, I’ll be covering my top 19 of the year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year in Books 2018</title>
      <link>/posts/2018-year-in-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 18:24:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2018-year-in-books/</guid>
      <description>Why So Many Books? Some of you might wonder why I chose to spend a lot of my free time in 2018 doing this instead of any of the other things with which I occupy my free time. The answer is simple: I love reading. It allows me to lose myself in another person’s world, learn from others’ experiences, and reflect constantly. It gives my mind a new dimension to explore.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
